人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    萌Su    小糯
校对：小糯          总监   小萌
时间轴：今        后期：加森目标糕富帅
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第五集
再快点  再快点  你这畜生
Faster, faster, you beast!
只能这么快了  吉恩
This is as fast as it goes, Gene.
有个轮子不太好使
It has a messed-up wheel.
还要推着一坨废物
And a lot of junk in the trunk.
要推的东西更多了
More to push.
没错  吉恩
Yes, Gene.
你自找的
You love it.
哔哔  火鸡城到了
Beep-beep! Here we are in Turkey Town.
你们好呀
Oh, hello, there.
你们这些幸运的家伙
Which one of you lucky fellas
这周四谁想上我的餐桌呀
wants to get eaten by me this Thursday?
-我  -不  我
- Me! - No, me!
好了  先别争  各位
Okay, settle down, everyone.
所以现在老爸是在跟火鸡说话吗
So dad's talking to turkeys now?
拜托  老爸  赶紧买个烤箱
Sheesh, dad. Get an oven.
你们老爸就爱过感恩节
Your dad loves Thanksgiving.
这是他最喜欢的节日
It's his favorite holiday.
会是你吗  你块头很大嘛
Will it be you? You're a big one.
-你在健身吗  -偶尔
- You been working out? - A little.
你看起来很棒
Well, you look great.
好吧  是有点怪
Yeah, it's a little weird,
不过他选火鸡的过程就是这样
but it's his selection process.
好像在看《单身汉》
It's like the <i>Bachelor</i>,
美国娱乐节目  类似国内《非诚勿扰》
只不过最后  选中的对象要被他吃掉
but at the end, the one he chooses gets eaten.
现实中的《单身汉》也是这样
That's what happens on the real <i>Bachelor</i>, too.
只是节目没播出来
They just don't show it on camera.
鲍勃  我怎么样
Hey Bob, what about me?
抱歉  我刚才没看见你
Oh, yeah. Sorry, I didn't see you there.
我希望他能等到回家再给它填陷
I hope he waits to get it home before he stuffs it.
是的  是的  就是你了
Yes. Yes, it's you.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
太感谢了
Hey, thank you so much.
我都不知道该说什么了
I don't know what to say.
好了  什么都不必说
It's okay, don't say anything.
鲍勃
Oh, Bob.
老爸  你哭了吗
Dad, are you crying?
好了  让他们好好说说话
Shh! Let them have their moment.
没错
Yes!
走吧  我们回家填火鸡去
Come on. Let's go get stuffing.
-走  -就是你了
- Come on. - You're the one!
-走啦  -就是你
- Come on! - You are the one!
那只火鸡成我们老妈了
That turkey is our mom now.
费舍奥德先生
Uh, Mr. Fischoeder.
还没到十二月吧
Um, it's not December yet.
十一月的房租我前几天刚交过了啊
And I, I paid November's rent a few days ago.
硬币是多了点  不过...
I know I used a lot of pennies, but...
别紧张鲍勃  我今天是你的朋友
Stand down, Bob. I'm just here as a friend.
一个需要借你家人过感恩节的朋友
A friend who needs to borrow your family for Thanksgiving.
啥
What?
我想和你们一家
I need to borrow your family
共进感恩节晚餐
for Thanksgiving dinner.
为啥
Why?
鲍勃  你爱过什么人吗
Bob, have you ever been in love?
严格来说  我正爱着呢
I-I guess. I-I technically am.
就是我
Hi!
鲍勃  我曾经也爱过一个人
Well, Bob, I was in love once, too.
真恶心
Oh, sick!
她叫谢尔比・施纳贝儿
With Shelby Schnabel,
继安妮・欧克丽之后最有名的神枪手
the most famous sharpshooter since Annie Oakley.
你爱谁我根本不感兴趣
You lost me at "love"
不过提到"神枪手"我的兴趣就来了
but brought me back with "sharpshooter".
她抛下我跟一个已婚的石油王老五跑了
She left me for a married oil magnate.
接着又抛下他跟一个已婚的电影王老五跑了
Then she left him for a married movie magnate.
她泡过的王老五还真多
She's a magnate magnet.
就是个破坏别人家庭的小三
More like a homewrecker.
完全正确
Exactly,
所以我才要给她提供一个可以破坏的家嘛
which is why I need to give her a home to wreck.
你要是想破坏你家
If you want to wreck your home,
买堆老鼠  用正常的方式
buy a bunch of mice, like a normal person.
鲍勃  我用一个月的房租来跟你做交换
So, Bob, in exchange for one month's rent,
能不能让你的家人装成我的家人
can your family pretend to be my family?
太好了  演戏耶
Yay! Acting!
不行
Mmm... No.
从现在开始  叫我吉恩・费舍奥德
From now on, call me Gene Fischoeder.
等等  叫我维苏威・费舍奥德
No, wait, Vesuvio Fischoeder.
不不  阿拉巴马・施莱默
No, wait, Alabama Slammer!
也有"阿拉巴马监狱"之意
你也要来  鲍勃
I'll need you, too, Bob,
扮成我的厨师  帮我料理火鸡
to pose as my cook and to roast the bird.
绝对不可能
Definitely not.
感恩节是我们全家最喜爱的节日
Thanksgiving is this family's favorite holiday.
怎么  难道不是
Wait, it's not?
当然不是  听好了
No way. Check the rankings.
我生日  圣诞节  万圣节
Here goes... My birthday, Christmas, Halloween...
-复活节  -光明节
- Easter. - Hanukkah.
下雪日  外行夜
Snow Day, Amateur Night...
好了  这个...
Uh, okay, that's...
-老兵节  -牙仙节
- Veterans Day. - Tooth Fairy Eve.
不是吧
Not real.
圣帕特里克节  劳动节
St. Patrick's Day, May Day,
爱尔兰的国庆节
土拨鼠节  《权力的游戏》新季首播日
Groundhog Day, season premiere of <i>Game of Thrones</i>...
你们根本没看过...
You've never even seen...
反对节
Opposite Day,
死人节
Day of the Dead...
-别说了  -活死人节  狂欢节
- Stop. - Dawn of the Dead, Carnival...
安杰拉・兰斯伯里的生日
Angela Lansbury's birthday...
英国女演员
-别说了  -洗澡夜
- No. - Bath Night...
黑色星期五
Black Friday,
然后才是感恩节
then Thanksgiving.
我喜欢黑色星期五
Love Black Friday.
甚至胜过感恩节吗
Black Friday before Thanksgiving?
没错  因为这节日很黑暗
Yeah, cause it's dark.
别闹了  各位
Oh, come on guys,
那我们的感恩节传统呢
what about all of our Thanksgiving traditions?
吉恩和我玩橄榄球
Gene and I always play football.
我只抱脚
Always go for the feet.
蒂娜和我掰许愿骨
Tina and I break the wishbone.
我想掰断更多的许愿骨
I wished for more wishbones.
露易丝和我呢  就用火鸡内脏
And Louise, we use the giblets
玩《火鸡现场调查・迈阿密篇》
to play Turkey Crime Scene Investigation: Miami.
死因是身首分离
Cause of death is a missing head.
去年也这样
Same as last year.
每年都这样
Same as every year.
我们要抓的是一个连环杀手
We've got a serial killer on our hands!
不过大家最喜欢的还是我的搞笑致辞  对吧
But everyone's favorite part is my funny toast, right?
比如  去年  我说的是
Like, last year, I said,
如果你想打开这个家的门
if you want to open the door to this family,
请用火鸡钥匙
use the tur-key!
火鸡...
Tur...
我的天  我才明白过来
Oh, my gosh. I just got it.
那我提高条件好了
Let's up the ante.
三个月的房租
Three months' rent.
鲍鲍
Bobby.
-两个月  -吉恩  闭嘴
- Two. - Gene, no.
紫色  我们这是在猜什么
Purple. What are we guessing?
-五个月  -成交
- Five. - Deal.
我没想到你真的...  那好
Wow, I didn't think you were gonna go... Okay.
这对我们来说真的意义非凡
Uh... well, that'll make a huge difference for us.
好像真的捡到钱了
That's-That's like real money.
很好  我会把感恩节的剧本发给你们
Goodie. I'll send you all scripts for Thursday.
希望你们好好揣摩自己的角色
I want you to really get into your parts.
就像我要好好揣摩谢尔比一样
Just like I'm going to get into Shelby's parts.
散发女性魅力的部位
Her lady parts.
散发女性魅力的部位是哪里
Which are the lady parts?
阴道和真心
The vagina and the heart.
真不敢相信
I can't believe
给金泽当伴娘时穿的礼服我还能穿下
my bridesmaid's dress from Ginger's wedding still fits me.
你看上去像一根优雅的香肠
You look like an elegant sausage.
但愿还有口气唱感恩节之歌
I hope I can breathe to do my Thanksgiving song.
说好不唱歌的
I thought we settled on no song.
我讨厌没有歌的剧本
I hate plays that don't have songs.
我会见缝插针的
I'll find a place to fit it in.
你的感恩节之歌怎么唱
What's your Thanksgiving Song?
别  别  别  别  别
Uh, no, no, no, no, no.
递我一下蔓越莓酱
Pass the cranberry sauce.
今天吃的是土豆泥
We're having mashed potatoes.
火鸡好棒
Ooh, the turkey looks great.
琳
Lin.
感谢爱我
Thank you for loving me.
琳
Lin.
感谢有你
Thank you for being there.
天哪
Oh, God.
每个人都在致谢
Everyone's thanking.
琳
Lin.
全世界都在致谢
The whole world's thanking you.
别唱了  琳  别唱了
Stop, Lin. Stop.
谢谢我们感谢你
Thanking us for thanking you.
琳
Lin.
宰了那只火鸡
Kill the turkey
饶了我吧
Please.
我觉得挺好的
I liked it.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了  大家  我们到了
Okay, everyone, we're here.
听好  我想到怎么过贝尔彻式感恩节了
Listen, I figured out how to have our own Thanksgiving:
在费舍奥德的感恩节里穿插进行
stuffed inside Fischoeder's Thanksgiving.
就像火鸭鸡那样
Like a turducken.
把鸭塞在火鸡里
A poultry within a poultry.
像是《盗梦空间》  肉中有肉
It's like <i>Inception</i>, with meats.
吉恩  开饭之前
Gene, before dinner,
你来厨房和我玩会抱摔
you come in and we'll play tackle in the kitchen.
然后换蒂娜进来掰许愿骨
Then send Tina in for the wishbone.
再来是露易丝
And then Louise.
八点一到
And at exactly eight o'clock,
你们都说要上厕所
you all say you have to go to the bathroom,
然后溜到厨房听我致祝酒辞
and then you come to the kitchen for my toast.
八点  这是暗示
Eight o'clock... that's your cue.
我没听全
I'm only half listening.
你刚才是要我们去厨房里的厕所吗
Did you just say you want us to go to the bathroom in the kitchen?
不是的  露易丝
No, Louise.
都过来  为"贝尔彻感恩节"加油  准备
Come on, guys, "Belcher Thanksgiving" on three, ready?
一  二...
One, two...
费舍奥德家的人
Ah, the Fischoeders!
进来吧  我的家人
Come inside, family.
好吧
Okay, uh...
你们进去
You guys go.
我还是很兴奋
I'm still excited.
可以开下门吗
Uh, can you open the door?
从后门进吧  厨子
Go around the back, cook.
好吧  还是会不错的
Okay. Still gonna be good.
这栋房子最初是由一个
This house was originally built
患有被害妄想症的砒霜制造商承建的
by a paranoid arsenic manufacturer.
我打赌这些柜子里肯定有真骷髅
Oh, I bet there are actual skeletons in these closets.
还有一个装满珍宝蟹的地牢
And a dungeon full of Dungeness crabs.
我打赌冲厕所时
I bet when you flush the toilets,
水分向上蒸发会出现彩虹
the water evaporates upwards and forms a rainbow.
有两个人说对了
Two of you are correct.
自己家里就别客气了
You already signed your liability waivers,
去探索一下吧
so go explore.
太棒了
Awesome!
那  费舍...
So, Mr. Fisch...
我说得果然没错
I was right about the toilets.
我还以为厨房风格会更  "庄园"一点
Huh, I thought the kitchen would be more, uh, "mansion-y".
庄园是给主人住的  鲍勃  不是厨子
Mansions are for the owners, Bob, not the cooks.
恕我失陪  我要去为晚餐喝醉了
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm going get drunk for dinner.
你是想说"更衣"吗
Do you mean dressed?
更衣  差点忘了
Dressed, out of my mind.
放松点  知道吗
Got to loosen up, you know?
对  对
Right, right.
我要换上色迷迷的表情
Got to get my sex face on.
好期待啊
I can't wait to see it.
琳  这样也不算太坏  是吧
Well, Lin, this might not be so bad, right?
感恩节这么过
This Thanksgiving.
-别  -怎么了
- Neh. - What?
我的发型
My hair!
又得重新弄了  真是的
Now I got to go redo it. Great.
好吧
Fine.
看来我只能待在这了  独自一人
Guess I'll just be here, alone.
和这个...  火鸡一起
With uh... With the turkey.
我叫兰斯
My name's Lance.
抱歉  和兰斯一起
Sorry. With Lance.
你好吗  兰斯
How are you, Lance?
相当好
Pretty great.
我的鱼宝宝们来啦
Oh, there are my little Fischies.
谢谢你送的这套新礼服
Thanks for the new outfits.
有时你得试试裸装风格
Sometimes you need a make-under.
很高兴你们喜欢
I'm glad you like them.
好了  今晚的任务就是
Now, our job tonight is to fool
欺骗我的梦中情人
the woman of my dreams
让她相信我们是相亲相爱
into believing that we are a loving,
又有机可乘的一家人
happy, nuclear family that she can destroy.
真浪漫
Romantic.
为了让你们更有动力
In order to keep you kids motivated,
我先说下游戏规则
we're going to be playing by arcade rules.
谁装得像费家小孩
You'll be awarded these tickets
谁就会得到这些奖券
for convincing performances as Fischoeder children.
游戏开始  等等  暂停一下
Game on. Wait, time out.
好了  重新开始吧
Okay, game on again.
我还以为鞋带开了呢
I thought my shoe was untied.
今晚结束之前奖券最多的人
The one with the most tickets at the end of the evening
可以在我的奖品室里领取一份礼物
can claim a gift from my prize room.
我唯一想要的礼物就是你的爱  父亲
The only prize I need is your love, father.
比赛这就算开始了
And we're off and running.
和所有幸福的家庭一样
And just like every happy family,
我们也请人画了一幅全家福
we now have a commissioned painting of us,
画里还有族徽  族徽上是十根鸡鸡
holding the family crest covered in ten schlongs,
德语里是"蛇"的意思
which of course is German for "snakes".
看看这些蛇啊
Look at the schlongs.
她来了
Oh, she's here!
She's here!
天啊  我好紧张
Oh, God. Oh, I'm so nervous.
各就各位  快点  各就各位
Places, people! Places!
准备好进烤箱了没
You ready for the oven?
我不确定  鲍勃  这感觉好奇怪
I don't know, Bob. It feels weird.
这种事应该在家里做
We should be doing this at home.
我知道今年有些不太一样
I know it's not the same,
不过也还是很有趣的
but it can still be fun.
不如尝一小口那个酒吧  鲍勃
Why don't you take a sip of that over there, Bob?
那个吗
That?
对  就是那个绿瓶子
Yeah, that green bottle.
这是  苦艾酒
It's, uh, absinthe.
喝了不会产生幻觉吗
Doesn't this make you hallucinate?
人生苦短
Carpe diem!
什么
What?
及时行乐
Seize the day.
好吧  我就尝一小口
All right, I'll take a little sip.
不会有什么大碍的
This can't be that bad.
好奇怪
Weird.
鲍勃  鲍勃  鲍勃
Bob! Bob! Bob!
怎么了
What?
烤箱里的灯能开着吗
Can you leave the oven light on for me?
我好怕怕
I get scared.
你真可爱
So cute.
给你开开了
Here's the light.
太亮了啦
It's too bright.
谢尔比  这是我的妻子  琳达
Shelby, may I present my wife, Linda.
很高兴见到你  琳达
Pleasure to meet you, Linda.
我喜欢你这名字  琳达
Oh, I like that name, Linda.
我就是琳达
And I'm Linda.
右边这些  是我的孩子们
Moving right along, these are my children,
吉娜  蒂姆  和露西
Gina, Team, and Lucy.
欢迎来到我们这个幸福之家
Welcome to our happy home.
我爸爸的前女友就是我的好朋友
Any ex-lover of my father's is a friend of mine.
这些小孩真是鬼灵精怪
What unusual children.
凯尔文  真不愧是你的种
Calvin, your sperm did wonderfully.
她夺走我的精子之后就为所欲为了
She took my sperm and ran with it.
因为我是他的...
Because I'm his...
因为我...
Because I...
因为我是他的妻子
Because I'm his wife.
谢谢你  琳达
Thank you, Linda.
说  你们几个喜欢子弹吗
Say, do you kids like bullets?
-小孩子都喜欢的  -反应快点
- I think all kids like bullets. - Think fast!
凯尔文  我的步枪你还留着呢
Calvin, you kept my old rifle.
这么多年你该不会还在喜欢我吧
You weren't carrying a torch for me all these years, were you?
当然不是
Oh, of course not,
我只是替你留着而已
I was just holding it for you.
你可以要回去的
You can have it back.
我想在这放两枪  你不介意吧
You don't mind if I cock this thing in here, do you?
随意
Cock away.
好大一声
Loud!
这一招叫"女骑男喷不完"
That trick's called the "Reverse Cowgirl".
我打赌你能从那射穿吉恩的耳朵
I bet you could pierce Gene's ear from there.
射我肚脐试试
Ooh, do my belly button!
不成年你甭想
Not till you're 18.
如果你教我射击
If you teach me to shoot,
我就叫你后悔教我射击
I'll teach you to regret teaching me to shoot.
我可以教你做汉堡  就像我们店的...
And I can teach you to make burgers like in our restaurant...
她在说什么呀
What is she talking about?
聊射击聊得我都渴了
All this talk about shooting is making me thirsty.
不如来杯酒解解"击"渴吧
Why don't we pull the trigger on a glass of wine?
好好笑
I'm funny.
我是他的风趣老婆
I'm his funny wife.
你很适合当家庭主夫  凯尔文
Being a family man suits you, Calvin.
比我记忆中的你强多了
You look better than I remember.
感恩节什么时候完事
When will Thanksgiving be over?
我想每天都过父亲节
I want it to be Father's Day every day!
非常好
Very nice.
来  父亲  我再给您斟上一杯
Here, father, let me refill your glass.
你已经伟大得脱水了吧
You must be dehydrated from being so wonderful.
多拿几张
Take it down a notch or two.
老爸  还记得我们一起做那种事吗
Hey, dad, remember when we did that thing?
真的好玩又难忘
That was fun and memorable?
真是悲哀
That's pathetic.
大家好  我是你们的厨师
Um, hello, I'm your chef.
没错  这位是我们的厨师  勃特
Yes, this is our chef, uh, Burt.
现在上的是沙拉  然后我要去
Here are your salads, and now I will, uh,
料理火鸡
go tackle the turkey.
听到了吗  吉恩
Did you hear that, Gene?
我要去  料理[抱摔]火鸡
I'm gonna go tackle the turkey.
赶紧去吧
Tackle away.
抱摔  火鸡
Tackle the turkey.
射得真准
That was a great shot.
真的  真的好玩
Really, really funny.
再射一发  用面包粒
Do another one. Ooh! Do a crouton.
不要  我现在要回厨房了
Uh, no, I'm gonna go back to the kitchen now.
那我  回去喽
So, uh, here I go.
回厨房喽
Back to the kitchen.
吉恩  去跟厨师道歉
Gene, go apologize to the cook.
吉恩  哥们  来玩球啊
Gene! Buddy, football time.
传统过法走起
Let the traditions begin.
那快点吧
Let's make this quick.
好的  我在一码线后持球
All right, I got the ball on the one-yard line
然后我会大喊
and then I gotta punch it in:
嘿一  嘿二
Hut, one! Hut, two!
嘿嘿嘿  嗨
Hut, hut, hut, hike!
干得漂亮  老爸  去洗澡吧
Great game, dad, hit the showers.
我们还没玩多久呢
But we barely played.
我要出去赢票
Gotta get out there and get more tickets.
票  你在说什么
Tickets? What are you talking about?
我没时间给你解释这么多
I don't have time to explain this to the help.
好吧  那把蒂娜叫来
Fine, just send Tina in.
我致辞时你得回来
And come back for my toast!
知道了  哥们
You got it, buddy.
我一口
One for me,
鲍勃一口
and one for Bob.
我很能喝这个的
I'm very good at drinking this.
谢谢
Thank you.
真是我的乖女儿
There's my girl!
好了  该掰许愿骨了  对吧
Okay, time to break the wishbone, right?
糟了  还在鸡身上呢
Oh, crap, it's still in the turkey.
好吧  那就早拔出来一会
Well, maybe we can just pull it out a little early.
我的天啊  好烫
Oh, my God, that's hot!
扯下来一块皮
Got some skin!
好  你抓着你那头  我们来玩许愿皮
Okay, you grab your end and let's do the wish-skin.
好的
Um, okay.
-太好了  你赢了  -耶
- Great, you won! - Yay.
你想许什么愿  更多的许愿皮
What'd you wish for, more wish-skins?
更多的票
More tickets.
最佳儿童比赛我落后了
I'm way behind in the best kid contest.
是吗  你要出去
Oh. So you're gonna leave?
我去把露易丝叫来
I'll send Louise in.
露易丝・贝尔彻遗憾地通知您
Louise Belcher regrets to inform you
她不能出席《火鸡现场调查・迈阿密篇》了
she can not attend the Turkey CSI: Miami
因为她与别人有约在先
due to a prior commitment.
好极了  我这算是白忙活了
Oh, great, I guess I did all this for nothing.
记住  鲍勃  这只是在演戏
Remember, Bob, it's all an act.
谢谢你  兰斯  是你一直支撑着我
Thanks, Lance, you've been my rock through all this.
我爱你
I love you.
好了  快八点了  我要致辞了
Well, it's almost eight o'clock, so I'll do my toast,
贝尔彻感恩节将会照常举行
and the Belcher Thanksgiving will be back on track.
我就"四"我
I "yam" what I "yam".
我"四"这世界上最幸运的男人
And what I "yam" is the luckiest man in the world.
这致辞怎么样  棒不棒
Was that a great toast or what?
你是最会致辞的致辞人
You're the toastest with the mostest.
一家人
Family!
过感恩节
Thanksgiving!
兰斯  你好大
Lance, you're big.
好奇怪啊  是不
This is weird, right?
我的老天
Oh, my God!
怎么了  怎么了  怎么回事
What? What! What's going on?
8:35了  我的致辞
8:35! My toast!
费舍奥德老爸  你好搞笑啊
Oh, Fischoeder Dad, you are hilarious!
他们不会来了  鲍勃
They're not coming, Bob.
我知道的  兰斯
Yeah, I know, Lance.
我的脸
Ow! My face!
鲍鲍  我需要切开的洋葱  快点
Bobby, I need a chopped onion... Stat!
没有人过来听我致辞  琳
No one came in for my toast, Lin.
我重要的致辞
My big toast.
你可以明天再致
You can do your toast for us tomorrow.
明天不是感恩节
Tomorrow's not Thanksgiving.
明天我们就可以免交五个月房租了
But tomorrow we'll have five months free rent.
因为这招管用  我觉得
Because this is working, I think.
快点  我需要洋葱帮我在下场戏里哭出来
Now come on, I need an onion so I can cry for my next scene.
快快[切切]  能懂吗
Chop-chop! Get it?
好啊  你们不想进来听我致辞
Fine. You don't want to come in here for my toast,
那我就去那致辞
I'll bring it out there.
不  你不会的  先生
No, you will not, mister.
歌我还没唱完呢
I haven't even done my song yet.
我要出去  琳
I'm coming out, Lin.
鲍勃  你喝醉了
Bob, you are drunk.
你才喝醉了呢
You're drunk.
没有了啦
I am not.
四瓶红酒我只喝了一半
I've only had half of four bottles of wine.
去拿火鸡过来  然后回到这里
Just bring the turkey out and you can come back in here
像在家里那样躺在地上打个盹  好吗
and take a nap on the floor like you do at home, okay?
好了  我要走了
Now, let's go!
-谢谢  -好棒
- Thank you. - All right!
谢谢  刚才的表演叫做"老爸颂"
Thank you. That was called "Ode To Dad".
真精彩
Bravo!
这个叫做"更好的老爸颂"
And this is called "Better Ode To Dad".
准备好了
Get ready!
这个我比不了
I can't compete with that.
我好感动啊
You know, I am so emotional.
你看我们这一家多热闹
What a wonderful... family we have.
我  我  我要感动哭了
And it's... It almost, it brings tears to my eyes. Hmm.
等一下
Just a second...
你表演得很棒  老妈
You're doing great mom.
非常自然
Really natural.
你可真逗乐
Oh, you are so married.
真他妈的逗乐
So gosh damn married!
大家好  是我  厨师
Hello, it's me, the cook,
鲍勃  或者勃特
Bob. Or Burt.
这位是兰斯
And this is Lance.
兰斯是只火鸡
Lance is a turkey.
兰斯  这些人就是我在厨房跟你聊天时
Lance, these are the jerks I mentioned in the kitchen,
提到的那些混蛋
when I was talking to you.
他看起来有希望赢
He seems like he's in a good place.
为了避免更多纠纷
So, without further ado,
现在由我致厨师辞
I will now give the traditional cook's toast
这是历年传统
that I do every year.
你应该回厨房去  厨师先生
Uh, maybe you should go back into the kitchen, Mr. Cook.
你给我闭嘴  费舍奥德夫人
Oh, shut up, Mrs. Fischoeder!
好吧
Uh, ah, okay.
厨房里肯定有五个月的盘子要洗
Wow, there must be five months of dishes to do in there.
你不想睡在地下室吧  厨师先生
You don't want to sleep in the basement again, Mr. Cook.
你怎么没完没了的
Are you still talking?
你不想没人给你暖...
You don't want to sleep without...
没  完  没  了  啦
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah!
天啊
Oh, dear!
继续感恩节致辞
It's Thanksgiving again,
有些"馅情"我想感谢
and there's some "stuff-ing" I'm thankful for.
递我一下蔓越莓...
Go on and pass the cranberries...
不要  琳  不要
Don't, Lin, don't!
-来首小曲吧  -闭嘴  住口
- It's time to sing a little song now. - Stop it! Stop!
越来越精彩了
Wow, this is getting good.
好  感恩节
All right... Thanksgiving.
我们来分析一下这个词
Let's break the word down.
-让我...  -谢谢
- Let me, uh, just... - Thanks.
-抱歉  在这  -人们经常使用这词
- Excuse me. Sorry. Up here. - I've heard people use that word quite often.
-我来"瓜"你两句  -比"更"经常
Let me just "pumpkin" you up by saying... Or than "than".
-"瓜你两句"  逗吧  -好像过"更多节"
- "Pumpkin you up." Right? - Than like we have "More Than Day"!
大家举杯
Let's raise our glasses.
-蒂娜  别举眼镜  -是的  请举杯
- Tina, drop those glasses. - Yes, raise your glasses.
再举高点
Raise them higher than that.
递我蔓越莓酱
Oh, pass the cranberry!
行了  闭嘴  琳
All right. Shut up, Lin!
就懒惰一会
Let's get a little lazy.
致辞结束  我说了算
Here's my toast, and what I say goes.
谁掌声多谁说了算
Me? We'll go by applause.
有谁喜欢厨师的致辞  请鼓掌
Everyone who liked the cook's toast best... Shh! Clap now!
我不需要掌声
I don't need clapping.
我想要的是每个父亲都想要的  拥抱
What I need is what every dad needs, hugging!
孩子们  过来抱抱爸爸  快来
Uh, kids, get go hug your dad. Come on.
不  是你们老爸  费舍奥德老爸
No, your dad, your Fischoeder Dad.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
-老婆  来呀  -好的
- Wife, come! - Oh, yes!
起作用了  上演压轴戏吧
It's working. Let's seal the deal.
-不要不要  -让我亲亲小嘴
- No, no. - Give me those lips.
-不嘛  -亲亲  -不嘛  -亲亲
- No. - Lips. - No. - Lips.
好吧  一下
Okay, one.
-哇  -恶心  -啊
- Whoa. - Sick! - Aw.
你给我放开她
Get your lips off her!
大家都想得到大家
Wow! Everybody wants everybody!
好兴奋哦
This is so exciting.
我相信厨师有很多酒要喝
I believe the cook has had too much to drink.
你这么认为吗
Oh, do you believe it?
我真心这么认为
I believe it in my heart of hearts.
好么  大家都听你说话了
Oh, great, everyone wants to hear your beliefs!
你给我回厨房
Back to the kitchen now!
就不回去
I'm not going back.
这才有节日氛围嘛
Now this is a holiday.
-我拿只腿行不行  -不行
- Is it cool if I grab a leg? - No.
你们根本不配吃兰斯
You people don't deserve to eat Lance.
兰斯是我的朋友  知道吗
Lance is my friend, okay?
兰斯  你烫着我的胳膊了
Ow, Lance, you're burning my arm.
放下那只火鸡
Put that turkey down.
我付你薪水和房租
I pay your salary and your rent.
留着你的臭钱吧  费舍奥德
Keep your blood money, Fischoeder!
鲍鲍  回来
Bobby, come back!
不许带走肉汁[黑钱]
Not the gravy!
给我留个鸡腿
Save me some dark meat!
兰斯  照顾好我爸爸
Lance, take care of my father!
带着火鸡回来
Get back here with that turkey!
我去要回来
I'll get it back.
我喜欢猎火鸡
I love a turkey hunt.
等等  什么
Wait. What?
他们抓不到我们的  躲这
They'll never catch us! Let's hide here.
在那呢
There he is!
天啊
Oh, boy.
趴下[鸭子]  鲍勃  趴下
Duck, Bob, duck!
你可是火鸡  兰斯
You're a turkey, Lance.
这句漂亮  鲍勃
Good one, Bob.
他们要追过来了
They're gaining on us!
两边跑
Run side to side!
好的  不过这样更慢了
Okay, but I think this is slower.
谢尔比  住手  不要打他
Shelby, stop! Don't shoot him!
搞什...
What the...?
带着火鸡回来  厨子
Come back here with our turkey, cook!
不要  他是我的
Never! He's mine!
不要  不要打我爸爸
No, don't shoot my dad!
不会的  我只想打那厨子
I'm not. I'm gonna shoot the cook!
而且我不会杀了他  我只想废了他
And I won't kill him. I'm just gonna maim him!
抱住摔倒
Tackle!
天啊  我们杀了鲍鲍
Oh, God, we killed Bobby!
我们杀了鲍鲍
We killed Bobby!
老爸
Dad!
他们为啥一直喊那厨子"爸爸"
Why do they keep calling the cook "dad"?
琳  他被射中了
Lin, he's shot.
谢天谢地  苍天啊
Oh, thank goodness. Oh, my God.
老爸
Dad!
兰斯  跟我说
Lance, talk to me.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
不  不  我挺不住了  鲍勃
No, no I'm not gonna make it, Bob.
不要这么说  兰斯
Don't say that, Lance.
不要这么说
Don't talk like that!
你会没事的
You're gonna be fine!
不  我冷  我好冷
No, I'm cold. I'm so cold.
去给他拿条毯子
Get him a blanket!
什么
What?
他在说什么
What's he saying?
不知道  听不懂
I don't know. I can't understand.
他在说什么
What's he saying?
只是在哼哼
He's just murmuring!
兰斯  兰斯
Lance? Lance?
他死了
Oh, he's gone!
鲍鲍  我很抱歉
Oh, Bobby, I'm so sorry about all this.
我再也不想当谁妻子了
I never want to be someone else's wife,
就是假扮也不行
even for pretend.
很抱歉我们毁了你的感恩节  老爸
Sorry we ruined your Thanksgiving, dad.
我们是混蛋
We were jerks.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry, too.
我答应你以后的每一天
I promise to tackle you every day
都会跟你玩抱摔
for the rest of my life.
我跟一只火鸡说了很久的话
I've been talking to a turkey for a long time now.
我喝了很多苦艾酒  坦白地说
But I drank a lot of absinthe, just to be fair.
鲍鲍  来亲一口
Oh, Bobby, come here.
琳  现在不是时候  我正在哀悼
Lin, not now, I'm grieving.
我今天失去了一个朋友
I lost a friend today.
我好迷惑
This is so confusing!
很明显  是这个厨子
Well, it's clear to me that this cook has, uh,
生的这些小孩  他是和这位...
fathered these, uh, children with, uh, this...
别说了
Oh, give it up.
我不是费舍奥德的老婆  好吗
I'm not Fischoeder's wife, all right?
他雇我们扮成他的家人
He hired us to pretend to be his family
这样就能吸引你了
so you'd be attracted to him, there.
我好感动  你愿意这么花心思
I'm touched that you would go to so much trouble
在一个小老太太身上
for a little old me.
你不老  也不小
Oh, you're not old, and you're not little.
你的那里
Not where it counts.
不算老
In the wabba-wabba.
凯尔文 这些都不管用
Oh, Calvin, this isn't gonna work.
我自尊心很强的
I respect myself too much
我不会成为别的女人
not to be the other woman.
你们真是疯了
Wow, you guys are insane.
咱们赶紧走吧
Let's get out of here.
我们还能赶上回家吃饭
We can still have dinner at home.
等等  差点忘了
Wait! I almost forgot!
我的票最多
I have the most tickets!
我很清楚自己想要什么
And I know exactly what I want.
现在起由这幅画替我长大
Now this portrait will grow old for me
我永远都是九岁
and I'll stay nine forever.
这瓶"不在酒"好好喝哦
Oh! This "Absence" is delicious.
是苦艾酒  琳
It's absinthe, Lin.
你是苦艾酒
You're absinthe.
老妈  你产生幻觉了吗
Hey, mom, are you hallucinating yet?
还没  我还要喝
Not yet. I need more.
好了  谁想要哪里
Okay, who wants what?
我想要被射中的那块
I'll take a bullet piece, please.
我也是
Me, too!
我想要鸡腿
I'll have a thigh.
弹片大家都有份的  别不好意思
There's plenty of shrapnel for everyone... don't be shy.
还好子弹打中的是兰斯
Good thing the bullet hit Lance,
否则我们就得吃老爸了
or else we'd be eating dad.
他的味道一定又老又苦
He'd taste old and bitter.
我敢说老爸做的饭一定很好吃
I bet dad would've made a great dinner.
谢谢你  蒂娜
Thanks, Tina.
你肉这么多
Yeah, you're so plump.
敬美味的鲍鲍
Aw, to delicious Bobby!
琳  别为了吃我敬酒
Lin, don't toast to eating me.
吃老爸  吃老爸  吃老爸
Eat dad! Eat dad! Eat dad!
停下
Stop!
吃鲍勃  吃鲍勃  吃鲍勃  吃鲍勃
Eat Bob! Eat Bob! Eat Bob! Eat Bob!
感恩节就此结束
Thanksgiving's over!
递我一下蔓越莓酱
Pass the cranberry sauce,
今天吃的是土豆泥
we're having mashed potatoes.
火鸡好棒
Ooh, the turkey looks great.
-感谢爱我  -琳
- Thank you for loving me. - Lin...
-感谢有你  -别
- Thank you for being there. - Please.
-感谢爱我  -天啊
- Thank you for loving me. - Oh, God.
-每个人都在致谢  -琳
- Everyone's thanking. - Lin...
全世界都在致谢
The whole world's thanking you.
琳 停下  琳  停下
Lin, stop. Lin, stop.
-谢谢我们感谢你  -琳
- Thanking us for thanking you. - Lin...
-宰了那只火鸡  -琳
- Kill the turkey. - Lin!
不  递我一下蔓越莓酱
No. Pass the cranberry sauce,
今天吃的是土豆泥
we're having mashed potatoes.
火鸡好棒
Ooh, the turkey looks great.
-感谢爱我  -琳
- Thank you for loving me. - Lin...
-感谢有你  -别
- Thank you for being there. - Please.
感谢爱我
Thank you for loving me.
-每个人都在致谢  -琳
- Everyone's thanking. - Lin...
-全世界都在致谢  -停
- The whole world's thanking you. - Stop.
谢谢我们感谢你
Thanking us for thanking you.
宰了那只火鸡
Kill the turkey.